[ man whistles ]
Hey , Frank ! Let 's wrap it up and go home .
What do you say ?
Well , I got another hour 's work to do .
The kid 's gonna stick with me , and then I 'll show him the ropes .
Okay . You lock up for me before you go ?
4th of July weekend , buddy boy . Got to move .
Oh , yeah . Yeah . Well , you have a nice 4th ,
and I 'll see you Sunday at the barbecue .
You 'd better believe it . I 'll be there with bells on .
Kid , I wanna tell you something , and I mean this sincerely .
No matter what happens , don 't name it after me .
[ laughs ]
Take it easy , Frank .
That Burt 's a joker .
Ok , Freddy , follow me and learn something .
Okay .
We got an order here from the St. Louis University Medical School .
They want two adult female skeletons with perfect teeth .
That 's a 2-AF-PT .
Ok ? So you come over here to the " A " section .
- That 's " A " for adult , see ? - Okay .
Then that 's divided up into two sections .
That 's divided into the " M " for male and the " F " for ...
- Female . - Good boy .
Now the " PT . "
Suppose you think that 's " pretty tough " , but no , that 's ...
- Perfect teeth . - Very good .
Now you get some excelsior over there and lay it in that crate .
Make a nice little beddy-bye for this little lady .
Okay .
Good work . We want her to be comfortable .
Now help me get her in . Grab her legs .
Okay .
Now you get some of that styrofoam popcorn ,
spread it all around .
Don 't be stingy . Uncle Burt 's paying for this .
More , Freddy , more . Ok , that 's fine .
Now spread it around . That 's right .
- You 're doing very nice work . - Thanks .
You 're gonna be fine in the warehouse business .
Where do we get all these skeletons from ?
- Oh , they come from India . - India ?
International treaty . All skeletons come from India .
No kidding . How come ?
How the hell do I know " how come " ?
The important question is ,
where do they get all the skeletons with perfect teeth ?
I 'm going to ask you a serious question .
How many people you know die
with a beautiful , perfect set of choppers in their puss , huh ?
Nobody I can think of .
No . I think that there 's a skeleton farm over in India .
[ laughs ] Jesus !
Come on , kid . Follow your uncle here .
Here we go .
I don 't have to tell you what these are for .
Ba ba ba boom !
Here we 've got the prosthetic devices , all around here .
Look under there . Wheelchairs .
Right . These are great .
Here 's something you don 't see very often .
You 're a privileged person .
These are split dogs . Yep , for veterinarian schools .
Oh , we get a lot of orders for split dogs .
- That 's really rad . - Yeah .
- [ growls ] - Don 't fool around , you 're learning .
Over here , Freddy , is where we keep the fresh cadavers .
We sell these to medical schools
and to the U.S. Army for ballistic tests .
Well , say hello .
We usually got more inventory than this ,
but , ah , we 're expecting a shipment on Monday .
H-how many bodies are in here usually ?
Well , you know , you don 't want to be overstocked .
Kind of like the restaurant business ,
you don 't want your inventory to lose its freshness .
[ laughs ]
Tell you what I 'll do , kid .
Teach you how to fill out these shipping forms .
Look alive .
- We gonna party tonight or what ? - Yeah , we are gonna party .
Well , where ? Where we gonna party ?
- I don 't know . Somewhere . - Hey , we could go to the park .
Oh , no , we can 't . The cops will shoot us if we go back to the park .
And I ain 't in no mood to die tonight .
I like death .
I like death with sex . How ' bout you , Casey ?
- You like sex with death ? - Yeah , so fuck off and die .
So , when we gonna party tonight , Tina ?
Oh you guys , that 'd be really rad ,
but I 'm supposed to meet Freddy when he gets off work .
Yeah , where you supposed to meet him ?
At this medical supply warehouse where he 's working .
Oh , no , he got a job ? What a dick .
Shit , why didn 't you say so ?
Why don 't we all go pick Freddy up ?
Freddy always knows where there 's a place to party .
Frank ?
Yeah , kid ?
What 's the weirdest thing you ever saw in here ?
Oh , kid ,
I have seen weird things come ,
and I have seen weird things go .
But the weirdest thing I ever saw
just had to cap it all .
Oh , yeah ? What 's that ?
Let me ask you a question , kid .
Did you see that movie , Night of the Living Dead ?
Yeah , yeah , that 's the one where the corpses
start eating the people , right ?
Sure . Wh-what about it ?
Did you know that movie was based on a true case ?
Come on , you 're shitting me , right ?
I 've never been more serious in my life .
That 's not possible .
I mean , they showed zombies taking over the world .
They changed it all around . What really happened was
back in 1969 , in Pittsburgh , at the V.A. hospital ,
there was a chemical spill
and all that stuff
kinda leaked down into the morgue
and it made all the dead bodies
kinda jump around as though it was alive .
What chemical ?
2-4-5-Trioxin , it 's called .
It was to kinda spray on marijuana or something .
And the Darrow Chemical Company
was trying to develop it for the Army .
And they told the guy who made the movie
that if he told the true story , they 'd just sue his ass off .
So he changed all the facts around .
So what really happened ?
Well , they closed it all down , see ,
and the Army shipped all that contaminated dirt
and all those dead bodies out .
And they kept it a secret . Shh .
What ...
So how come you know about it ?
A typical Army fuck up .
The Transportation Department got the orders crossed ,
and they shipped those bodies here
instead of to the Darrow Chemical Company .
[ telephone rings ]
Hello ?
Oh , hi , honey .
Uh , no , I 'll be home in about an hour .
You keep the , uh , pot roast hot , okay ?
Yeah , sure , I love you , too , honey . Yeah . Kiss , kiss .
Wanna see them ?
- See them ? - The corpses .
What are you talking about ?
- They 're down in the basement . - No .
- Come on . - No way .
[ door creaks ]
Hey , mind the third step . It 's a bitch .
You mean , they just brought those bodies here and left them ?
Well , you know the Army .
And they 've been here all this time ?
14 years , as I recall .
No kidding ?
There they are .
There 's bodies in there ?
[ squeaking ]
Oh , shit . Look at that .
- You say that thing was alive ? - So they say .
Oh , God .
- Hey , these things don 't leak , do they ? - Leak ? Hell , no .
These things were made by the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers .
Oh , fuck ! [ coughs ]
[ choking ]
[ soft classical music plays ]
Hello , dear . How was your day ?
The usual , crap .
Oh , I 'm sorry .
What 's for dinner ?
Your favorite , lamb chops .
I had them for lunch .
Yes , it 's me , checking in from Station 3 at 1600 - -
uh , make that 1601 hours .
I 'll be home all evening . Right .
[ phone dialing ]
It 's nerve-racking to live around that equipment all the time .
They have to be able to reach me 24 hours a day , wherever I am .
You know that .
All that microwave stuff affects my oven .
When we find them , you can have the equipment taken out .
But when will you find them ?
Christ , Ethel , I don 't know !
Maybe we 'll never find them .
Look , we 've been through all this before .
They could be anywhere .
[ hard rock music plays ]
Where the fuck we going , anyway ?
- To party ! - To pick up Freddy .
Oh , yeah , what the fuck is Freddy up to these days , anyway ?
- He got himself a job . - Oh , no shit ? What job ?
- He 's a stockroom clerk . - Yeah ? That sounds like a shitty job .
Well , it isn 't the President of the United States ,
but at least he makes money to buy stuff .
Oh , yeah , maybe he 'll buy something from me ?
He don 't like your kind of stuff , Suicide .
How come you guys only come ' round when you need a ride someplace ?
' Cause you one spooky motherfucker , Suicide .
Oh , you think I 'm spooky , huh ? What the fuck !
[ bell sounds ] [ all yelling ]
Man , what a hideous , ugly place .
- I like it . It 's a statement . - Come on , let 's go get the prick .
- No . - Why not ?
- You might freak out his boss . - Well , that 's not nice .
Yeah , what does he think we are , weird or something ?
- What time does Freddy get off ? - 10 : 00 .
I ain 't sittin ' here two fuckin ' hours .
We could always go drive around .
I don 't got gas . You wanna buy some gas , idiot ?
I was kidding .
We could go fool around in there for a while .
You mean that cemetery ? Ahh .
Oh , let 's do that .
[ engine roars ]
What do you want to do , Scuz , turn over gravestones ?
No , I just want to look around the graveyard .
I ain 't never seen one before .
Ain 't you never been to a funeral ?
I never knew nobody that died .
I don 't think this is such a good idea .
- What 's that ? - Road flares , as swipe .
- What do you want those ? - I just want to party .
What are the road flares for ?
[ Scuz laughs ]
[ crickets chirp ]
This place is a mess .
[ crows squawk ]
This looks like your pad , Scuz .
I heard that .
[ hard rock music plays ]
[ coughs ]
Frank ?
[ gagging ]
Are you okay , kid ?
I don 't know . I don 't - - I don 't feel so good .
Christ , what a stink .
[ coughs ]
What the hell happened to the body ?
It must have melted when it hit the air .
Close the goddamn thing .
[ coughs ]
Christ , I never smelled anything like that before .
I think I 'm gonna be sick . [ wretches ]
[ vomits ]
[ coughs ]
[ coughing ]
Listen , I don 't guess we 'd better tell Burt about this .
It makes us look stupid or something .
I can still smell that stuff .
It must be in my nose , either that or it 's all over everything .
Yeah , I 'd better spray some deodorant around here .
[ coughs ]
Oh .
[ dog whimpers ] What was that ?
- Sounds like a dog . - A dog ?
Wait a second . Listen . Listen .
[ dog panting ] You hear that ?
What the hell 's going on here ?
[ coughs ]
[ dog panting ]
What 's wrong with him ?
[ dog whimpers ]
Oh , shit ! [ both scream ]
What are we gonna do ?
We 're gonna kill it !
[ dog yelps ]
What are you doing ? Stop !
[ screams ]
[ distant screaming ]
[ pounding on door ]
Aah !
Oh , Jesus ! Jesus !
[ screaming ]
Are we fucked ? What 's happening ?
It 's the cadaver ! The cadaver !
- What 's it doing in there ? - I don 't know . It sounds sore !
Well , what are we going to do ?
- Lock it in . - Yeah ! Yeah !
Oh , Jesus !
Hurry ! Jesus Christ !
We gotta think ! We gotta think !
Come on , son , get in there !
Oh , Jesus Christ !
Are we going crazy ?
No , it 's that crap from the tanks .
The goddamn chemicals , it 's all over everything .
Stupid asshole !
Watch your tongue , boy , if you like this job .
Like this job ?
- Think ! Think ! - We gotta call the cops .
No , you don 't want to call the cops .
You know what they 'd do to this company ?
- Who cares about the company ? - Well , think of our reputation !
Fuck your reputation .
Think ! Think !
What about the number on the side of the tank ?
The one that said to , " Call in case of an emergency . "
No , that 's the Army .
You don 't want the goddamn Army around this place .
- Think ! - Well , what are we gonna do ?
What are we gonna do ? We 're gonna call the boss .
Burt ? Frank .
We have a little problem .
[ distant screaming and pounding ]
Do you ever fantasize
about being killed ?
Never .
Do you ever wonder
about all the different ways of dying ,
you know , violently
and wonder , like ,
what would be the most horrible way to die ?
I try not to think about dying too much .
Mmm .
Well , for me
the worst way
would be for a bunch of old men
to get around me
and start biting
and eating me alive .
I see .
First ,
they would tear off my clothes .
Let 's get some light over here .
Trash is taking off her clothes again .
♪ In darkness you will find me ♪
♪ I dance among the dead ♪
♪ But very soon I 'll need to hunt ♪
♪ The scent of blood instead ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ We 'll make love ' till we die ♪
♪ We 'll make love ' til ... ♪
That 's right . Throw it , baby .
Hey , are you high on anything ?
♪ I know you think I 'm nasty ♪
♪ But I am no common girl ♪
♪ I once slept with the devil ♪
♪ It was really no big thrill ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ We 'll make love ' til we die ♪
You did what ?
You opened it ? You stupid moron .
You idiot . What 's the matter with you , Frank ?
Haven 't I always told you never to even
go near those goddamn tanks ?
[ screaming and pounding ]
What are we gonna do , Burt ?
I 'll tell you what I 'm gonna do .
I 'm gonna be sued by the Darrow Chemical Company ,
I 'm gonna be investigated by the government .
I might become famous , Frank , I might even lose my business .
I might even go to jail , goddamn it .
That 's what I 'm gonna do .
[ banging on door ]
On the other hand , we destroy all this evidence around here
and we keep our mouths shut .
That 's it ! Let 's do that , Burt !
Yeah , Frank , you 're right . That 's what we got to do .
One question , Frank .
This guy screaming in here , you 're sure he 's a dead cadaver ?
Why don 't you open the door and find out ?
No , that 's all right , Frank . I 'll take your word for that .
If it is a reanimated body , we 're going - - we 'll have to kill it .
[ screaming ]
How do you kill something that 's already dead ?
Well , how do I know , Fred ? I don 't know , let me think .
It 's not a bad question , Burt .
In that movie , they destroyed the brain to kill them .
- Is that what they did ? - The brain , right . Yeah .
What do doctors use to crack skulls with ?
- Surgical drills . - Here , hold this , Frank .
Now listen to me , both of you , very carefully .
Freddy , you 're gonna open that door .
Come here , you stand right over here . Frank , right here .
When it comes out , you brain it with that axe .
Oh , Jesus !
Well , how am I gonna stop it from moaning ?
What 's the matter with you , Frank ?
Fred , come here . Get down there . Please , stand by the door .
It 's gonna be all right , son .
I don 't think I can do this , Burt .
Well , you damn well better . You got us into this .
Oh , Jesus !
All right , Freddy . 22 , right .
[ door shaking ]
[ moaning ]
Oh !
Be brave , Frank , goddamn it !
4 , left .
10 , right .
[ door shaking ]
[ moaning ]
[ corpse screams ]
Aah !
Get him off , Frank !
[ crash ]
[ all yell ]
[ all scream ]
Coming for it , Frank .
Hold it !
Aah !
- [ corpse screams ] - Oh !
Oh ! Oh !
What the hell 's going on , Burt ?
The brain ! The brain !
I hit the fucking brain !
Then do something else , for goddamn-it-to-hell 's sake .
Hold him down , Frank .
I can 't stand this any longer .
- Oh , shit ! - Hold him down , now , hold him down ,
What are you gonna do ? Oh !
Be a man , Frank ! Be a man !
I can 't stand this , you son of a bitch .
Hurry up !
[ Frank screams ]
Oh , no !
[ all scream ]
- I 'll get him ! - Get him !
- I got him . - Get a rope !
Where the fuck 's a rope ?
I don 't know . Get one . Hold him down !
- [ Frank ] Are you hanging on ? - Got him !
Hang on to the son of a bitch !
Christ , it ain 't dying .
I thought you said if we destroyed the brain , it 'd die !
- It worked in the movie . - Well , it ain 't working now , Frank .
You mean the movie lied ?
Oh , Jesus .
Ah !
How are we gonna kill it ?
Maybe you can 't kill it . Maybe it won 't die .
Then we just got to destroy it completely
until there 's nothing left .
Acid .
What kind of acid would dissolve a body ?
Sulfuric acid , maybe .
No , no , aqua regia , that 's stronger .
But what if it doesn 't dissolve everything , like the bones ?
[ moans ]
Shit !
What are we gonna do ?
Burt ?
Where are you going ?
Sometimes Ernie Kaltenbrunner works late on Friday nights .
Well , who 's Ernie Kaltenbrunner ?
He 's the embalmer at the mortuary across the street .
What the hell 's he gonna do for us ?
His light 's on . He 's in .
Ernie 's got a crematorium across the street , Frank .
A crematorium , that 's beautiful .
You think you can get him to go along with it ?
I don 't know . I 've known Ernie about 25 years .
He might do it out of friendship . I 'm not sure .
Yeah , but what the hell are you gonna tell him ?
I mean , can you trust that bastard ?
I don 't think we have a choice , Frank .
How we - - how we gonna get this thing over there ?
Give me the bone saw .
[ hard rock music plays ]
Why don 't you put your clothes on ? The show 's over .
What 's the matter ? does it make you nervous ?
I 'm hot .
Yeah . You are hot .
Scram , wimp .
Nobody understands me , you know that ?
I fuckin ' bust my ass for you guys , and what do I get ?
" You 're spooky . "
Fuck you , man . Fuck you all .
I like it spooky .
I mean , I got somethin ' to say , you know ?
What do you think this is all about ?
You think this is a fuckin ' costume ?
This is a way of life !
Oh , yes .
Hey , what 's wrong with you , man ?
Show some fucking respect for the dead , will ya ?
- Hey , is that Freddy ? - Where ?
Over there , going in the building .
Nope . That is not Freddy .
How would you know ?
Because . Why would Freddy be going into a mortuary ?
[ classical music plays ]
[ knock at door ]
Damn !
What do you say , Ernie ?
Hey , Ernie .
Whoa !
- Take it easy . - Sorry , I didn 't hear you .
Fast on the draw .
Whew .
You are working late tonight .
Oh , yeah , yeah . Pretty much . Kind of ...
What time is it ? You want a cup of coffee ?
Uh , no . No , thank you . I 'm all right .
I do , and I need it .
What , uh , what are - - what are you doing there , Ernie ?
Breaking out the rigor mortis .
Oh , yeah ?
Come here .
- Huh ? - Come on .
You see , rigor mortis starts in the brain .
And it spreads down to the internal organs ,
and it finally settles in the muscles .
[ clears throat ]
It , uh ,
loosens up after a while , but , uh , you can , uh ,
you can break it out manually , as they say
by flexing the muscles . See that ?
Yeah .
You 'll not find that in a book , my friend .
The embalming business is basically passed on by word of mouth .
I 'll tell you , that 's fascinating , Ernie , that 's really something .
Well , he 's dead now . And | I am bushed .
Hey , uh , buddy boy . Uh ,
how long we been friends , Ernie ? About how long ? About ...
- 25 years , give or take . - Yeah .
Uh , if I ask you a favor , could you keep it quiet ?
Sure . What is it ?
Well , I 'm gonna need some help , Ernie ,
in a pretty big way , really .
You can depend on me . Why ? What 's wrong ?
Uh , I got a couple of my men out here , y-you mind if I let them in ?
B-Burt , that 's illegal .
You can bring it on in now , please .
Fred , you can put it right over here . Right here .
What is that ?
Right there , please .
- Here ? - Yeah .
I got to ...
Yeah .
What the hell is in those bags ?
- Rabid weasels . - What ?
What the hell are you doing with rabid weasels ?
I was trying to explain it to you . They came as a shipment .
' Course , they weren 't supposed to be rabid ,
you know , but you know how these things happen .
No , I don 't . How do they happen ?
Watch out ! Watch out , Ernie . Don 't get bit .
Yeah .
Anyway , we got them , and we need your help .
How ?
We got to get rid of these things .
Well , why don 't you call an animal shelter ?
Well , word 'd get out , hurt my business .
You know , that 's a bad scene , rabies .
I don 't think so .
I mean , so what ? You don 't run a pet store .
So , some lab animals got rabies .
Come on , guys , take them to the pound .
Well , I just can 't do that .
You got to - - you got to take my word for it .
What the hell do you want me to do ?
- You have a crematorium , right ? - You wanna burn them ?
Yeah , that 's what I had in mind , actually .
That 's cruel .
I can 't think of anything else to do .
Y-y-you just can 't burn animals alive .
It 's just too hideous .
At least let me kill them first .
Take ' em out in the parking lot , and put ' em out of their misery .
I don 't think that 'd work , Ernie .
I don 't — I don 't u-understand what 's going on . W-Why not ?
Can you swear to keep a secret , Ernie ?
At this point , I don 't know .
No , no , y-you got to swear .
You got to , or I just - - I can 't tell you .
All right , I swear .
Good .
It 's not weasels in the bags .
No . No kidding . Look here .
Oh !
Get it off !
Get it off ! Get it off !
Frank !
[ screams ]
[ moans ]
I 'm sorry , Ernie .
No , it 's all right .
[ clears throat ]
Ernie , we got a ...
We got a long story to tell you .
Oh , great . Some party .
What happened to Trash and Suicide ?
Probably getting it on somewhere .
Don 't even think it , Chuck .
Oh , God , when 's 10 : 00 gonna come ?
Hey , if you wanna split , we could both go somewhere .
You 'd really like to do it with me , wouldn 't you ?
Hey , I mean , a girl like you and a guy like me .
Go choke a chicken .
Oh , come on , Casey . I was only kidding , for sure .
Oh , great , here 's your friend and mine .
Hey , fuck you , ball buster .
Hey , my watch stopped . What time is it ?
Going on 10 : 00 .
Oh , fudge . I 'd better get over and find Freddy .
He 's gonna be getting off any time now .
OK . Go ahead , we 'll wait for you .
- Don 't go anywhere , okay ? - All right .
[ Spider chatters ]
[ Casey laughs ]
[ siren sounds ]
[ ring ]
Come on , Freddy , where are you ?
Frankly , Burt ,
I think you acted precipitously in cutting up the corpse .
Well , you may be right , I don 't know , but I did it .
So what - - what are we gonna do about it , Ernie ?
If I let you use the crematorium , what 's in it for me ?
What do you want ?
Well , uh ,
the way I see it , this is a pretty big favor .
Well , Ernie , you got it ! Whatever it is you want ,
so help me , I 'll - - I 'll do it . I promise .
I 'm sorry about that .
[ sighs ]
All right . Let 's take care of your problem .
Yes siree ,
you 're gonna owe me a big one .
Now buddy-boy , you go get rid of everything for me . Nothing left .
- Is that right ? - Everything 'll go .
What about the bones ?
Bones are no problem .
The hardest thing to burn is the heart .
The heart ? Why ?
' Cause it 's just one big , tough muscle .
Yeah , but Ernie , I mean , come on . We don 't - -
We don 't want the heart sticking around .
Then I 'll turn it up hotter for the heart .
And what about the split dogs ? They got to go , too .
The split dogs will go , too .
Come on , just give me a hand . It 's your mess .
Oh . [ groaning ]
Some big favor .
I can operate that goddamn thing .
You 're absolutely certain
that this will get rid of everything and do the trick ?
- I mean , nothing left ? - Nothing but a little pile of ashes .
We don 't even want the ashes , Ernie .
Well , then I 'll turn it up higher , and we 'll burn up the ashes , too .
Dust to dust .
[ lightning cracks , thunder rumbles ]
- Oh , my radio . - Come on , you guys .
Let 's get back to the car . Damn it .
Come on .
Freddy ?
Anybody ?
Get the fuckin ' top ! Fuck .
Get the fuckin ' top , man !
Come on !
Close the motherfuckin ' windows .
I don 't have any windows . I busted them .
- Hey , my skin burns . - Me , too . Damn it .
It 's that rain , it 's like acid rain .
Start the car !
It 's all over me . A towel , somebody give me a towel .
- We ain 't got no towel ! - Well , then give me something .
- Give me that . - No !
Give me something !
Come on , start !
- Suicide , get the car going . - I 'm trying .
Oh , crap , I wonder what 's in that rain .
Look at it .
It 's coming down like , einen getrunken soldat .
- Is the heart gone , Ernie ? - It 's all burned up .
- Are you sure ? - Right up the chimney .
Goddamn , that 's all we need . We 're home free , Frank .
We got it made . You just saved our ass , buddy boy ,
and I owe you one . Goddamn !
Yes , you do .
Alright , let 's get back to that warehouse , clean up the mess ,
and get the hell out of there .
What do you say , Frank ?
Okay , just - - just give me a second to rest ,
catch my breath . Then we 'll do it , okay ?
Frank , I don 't know about you , but I 'm really sick .
Why ? What 's wrong , Fred ?
I feel like hell is what 's wrong .
- I 'm really sick . - I 'm sick , too , Burt .
Sick , like how ?
I feel like my head 's going to bust wide open .
And I want to puke .
And I 'm weak , too .
Me , too . I got the chills .
It 's that stuff , Burt .
It 's that goddamn stuff we breathed .
What stuff ? What are you talking about , Frank ?
When that canister cracked , this gas squirted out .
It hit us right in the face .
We breathed it .
It knocked us out .
We were out cold , unconscious for a while .
Oh , Christ ! Ernie .
Shouldn 't we get to a doctor or - - or something like that ?
Yeah , Burt , I need a doctor .
Man , I 'm getting the car
and taking these guys to the emergency ward right now .
Let 's go , Frank . You 're gonna be alright .
We 're gonna get you there .
Hey , Frank !
Frank !
[ wretches ]
[ vomits ]
Come here , Ernie .
What 's the matter ? Talk to me . Get him out of the rain .
I gotta — I gotta call my wife . I gotta go to the hospital !
You can 't run around in this storm . You 're too sick .
Burt .
Take it easy . Take it easy .
I 'm gonna call an ambulance .
Paramedics . Paramedics .
It 's all right . How do you feel now ?
[ thunder claps ]
Hello . Yes .
Uh , can we get some paramedics over here right away ?
That 's the Resurrection Funeral Home
at 21702 East Central .
Uh , well , tell them to come around the back , to the embalming room .
Uh , no , no , um ...
Poison . We have two men poisoned here .
Uh , well , no , we - - we don 't know what kind of poison .
Right .
Thank you very much . Bye .
Burt , they 're on their way .
[ engine turning ]
This car ain 't going nowhere .
- Damn it . - Shh-shh !
Do you hear something ?
Hear what ?
Something .
[ distant moaning and wailing ]
[ pounding ]
No , I don 't hear nothing .
This roof 's leaking .
- There 's a rip , damn it . - Shit .
Oh , don 't do that !
- Shit ! - I 'm sorry .
Shit , Scuz !
Hello , there ?
Freddy ?
Anybody ?
Freddy ? Are you here ?
[ creak ]
Anybody here ?
Who 's there ?
Brains !
[ screams ]
Hey , I got to get out of here .
Let 's go to where Tina and Freddy are .
- Damn right . - Fuckin ' A.
[ gasping ]
Live brain .
[ screams ]
Come on , quick !
God , my skin 's really burning .
[ winch clanking ]
[ sobs ]
Hey , Tina !
[ Tina ] Yes ! Oh , God ! Help me !
- That 's Tina . - What 's she yelling about ?
- What 's that sound ? - Through that door !
[ Tina ] Help !
Watch the fuckin ' step !
Help me !
What the fuck ?
[ Tina screeches ]
Brains !
[ screams ]
More brains .
Where the fuck you going ?
Help me bar the door ! Stupid fuckers !
[ siren wails ]
[ knock at door ]
It 's them .
Who took the poison ?
Right over there .
Stick your tongue out for me .
What did you guys take ?
It was some kind of industrial chemical ,
I think , something in a tank .
What tank ? Where ?
Well , we - - we 're not sure , really .
Well , can you find out ?
I mean , your friends ' lives may depend on it .
Yeah , well , I got to make some phone calls ,
but I — I can 't do that before morning . I 'm sorry .
Let 's take some vital signs .
[ squeezes pump ]
- Can I borrow your stethoscope ? - What 's the matter ?
I can 't hear anything through mine .
Well , are you sure it 's the equipment ?
What do you mean ?
Well , I 'm not getting anything on this , either .
What do you mean ? What 's wrong ?
What 's wrong ?
It 's all right . We just need to double check a couple things .
- No blood pressure . - No pulse .
Well , what do you mean , " No blood pressure , no pulse " ?
Shh . Take it easy . Take it easy .
[ beeping ]
- What do you have ? - 70 .
- 70 what ? - 70 degrees .
- Well , what 's that ? - Room temperature .
Come over here for a second . I want to talk to you .
[ whispers ]
What are you guys saying ?
[ pounding on the door ]
What was that thing down there ?
- What the fuck are we gonna do ? - Hey , Suicide 's down there .
No way man , he 's gone . That thing ate his head .
Shh ! Shh !
I don 't hear anything down there , do you ?
Oh , we got to call somebody .
- Who ? - The cops .
I don 't wanna call no cop . The cops are just gonna kick our ass .
Just let 's get out of here , okay ?
No ! We gotta call somebody .
Wait a minute , where 's Freddy ?
He was gone , he wasn 't here when I showed up .
[ thunder claps ]
Holy shit . We 're gonna have to swim to get over there .
[ strange moaning ]
What the fuck was that ?
Look ! There !
[ thunder claps ]
♪ Do you wanna party ♪
♪ It 's party time ♪
[ screams ]
♪ We gotta party ♪
♪ It 's party time ♪
♪ Do you wanna party ♪
[ screams ]
Hey , wait up , you guys ! Wait , I got no shoes !
♪ It 's party time ♪
[ screams ]
No ! No !
You have no pulse , your blood pressure 's zero over zero ,
you have no pupillary response ,
no reflexes , your temperature is 70 degrees .
W-What does that mean ?
It 's a puzzle , because technically , you 're not alive .
Except you 're conscious , so we don 't know what it means .
- Are you saying we 're dead ? - Let 's not jump to conclusions .
Obviously , I didn 't mean you were really dead .
Dead people don 't move around and talk .
[ banging ]
- What 's the hell 's that ? - Front door .
- What the fuck are they doing ? - I 'll find out .
Listen we 're gonna go get a couple of stretchers .
Just hang in there . W-we won 't be a second .
[ girl screams ]
Open the door .
Open the door , please .
Help !
Hey ! Open the door !
Open the door !
Hurry up !
Freeze , or you 're dead !
Don 't shoot , man !
Are you crazy ? Are you on PCP ?
None of us are on any drugs , man . Just let us in !
All right , come in , come in . But no funny moves .
Shit , no .
You gotta lock all your doors and your windows ,
and call the cops ! They 're out there !
- What ? Who 's out there ? - Don 't you hear that ?
- What ? - Shut up and listen , man !
[ distant screaming and moaning ]
What is it ?
- It 's dead people screaming . - What dead people ?
They came from out of the ground .
And they 're after us .
Out of the ground ?
Our friends took off the other way . And they 're out there now !
[ corpses moan ]
Brains !
- Trash ? Where 's Trash ? - Didn 't she go with them ?
I thought she was with us .
- Hey , do you hear that ? - Hear what ?
[ screaming and moaning ]
Christ , Jesus .
What is that ?
It sounds like people screaming .
You get the stretchers , I 'll get on the radio and phone this in .
[ starts engine ]
[ screams ]
Jerry ?
Brain !
Brain ! Brain !
What ? What kind of a problem ?
Take a look at it .
Why , what the hell 's going on out here ?
Mister , that graveyard out there 's full of people
coming out of the ground .
Whaddya mean " out of the ground " ?
Yes , out of the ground .
They 're horrible , they scream , you 've got to do something .
Scream - - ?
Yes , mister , they 're out there .
And there 's one of them in that warehouse .
- Which - - which warehouse ? - The medical supply house .
Oh , shit ! Shit !
- And they 're - - - Goddamn !
I-I-I think things are getting out of hand .
Mister , there 's 100 of those things out there .
100 ?
The cops . We got to call the cops .
Yeah . No shit .
Phone . Where the fuck is the phone ?
There ! There 's an office !
Hello , operator , give me the police . This is an emergency .
[ screams ]
Grab the hammer and nails ! Casey !
Quiet ! Let 's just get the hell out of here , Ernie .
- You got a car ? - I got a car .
Get your keys . Let 's get out of here .
My clutch is shot .
We 'll use the paramedic ambulance .
Freddy ! Oh !
- Ernie ? - Yeah ?
Where are the paramedics ?
I 'll get them . Get my own car started .
Oh , my god , Freddy ! What did they do to you ?
[ screams ]
- Oh , God ! - What was that shooting ?
- Oh , God ! - What ? What , Ernie ?
God !
- Oh , God ! - What the hell ?
It ...
It !
" It " ? It what ? What is " it " ?
They 're all over the cars .
It 's horrible . They 're out there . They 're ...
Paramedics are dead . And we - - we can 't take the cars . We - - I — Burt ,
we 've gotta - - we 've gotta call the police .
Set him down . Set him down .
Set him down . Easy .
It 's not - - not - - not it 's not working .
Come on .
- What 's the matter ? - Dead .
[ glass breaking ]
Brains ! Brains !
Help me .
[ corpses moan ]
You got some hammer and nails ?
♪ Ooh , baby , your ♪ ♪ asphalt eater hung ten ♪
♪ The hoedads and gremmies ♪ ♪ say you reached top end ♪
♪ So do the dead , through the lights ♪
♪ The surf in ' dead , ooh , make it tight ♪
♪ The livin ' dead , now , ♪ ♪ baby , lose their heads ♪
Where else can they get in here ?
The windows in the chapel .
♪ You 're a high-rev hauler ♪ ♪ with all four on the floor ♪
Is there anything to board these windows with ?
I don 't think we have to . I put boards outside the glass .
♪ Come on , the livin ' dead , ♪ ♪ ooh , you 're in the soup ♪
♪ The livin ' dead , now , baby ♪
♪ Like I said , now , baby , do the dead ♪
♪ Now , do it ♪
[ woman over radio ] Rescue 7 , Rescue 7 , come in . This is dispatch . Over .
Rescue 7 , come in . This is dispatch . Do you copy ? Over .
Come in , dispatch .
Send
more
paramedics .
[ pounding ]
How many fuckin ' windows you got in this place ?
No more windows .
The embalming room has steel shutters .
Well , let 's get the hell back to the embalming room then . Come on .
Man , my arms are dead .
Put that goddamn thing down , Ernie ,
before you hurt somebody with it .
- How they doing ? - Buddy , are you all right ?
- It hurts . - What did you do to Freddy ?
What 's wrong with him ? And this man ?
I think it 's time you tell us what the fuck 's going on .
I don 't have to tell you anything , dick brain .
We think you should .
Tell them , goddamn it !
Tell us !
There was a chemical .
It was some chemical that soaked into the soil
of the graveyard and made the corpses come back to life .
Yeah ? What fucking chemical ?
I don 't know what chemical , goddamn it !
It was ordered by the military , I think . I think it was .
Would you tell me me how the fuck did it get all over the graveyard ?
I don 't know . I just ...
All I know is that it was stored
over at the medical supply warehouse
where you were , and these two geniuses
managed to open the goddamn container
and let the son of a bitch out . Let ' em out !
Is that why Freddy 's sick ?
I breathed it , Tina .
So did - - so did Frank there .
What did it do to you , Freddy ?
I 'm freezing .
My muscles are stiffening up .
Stiffening up ?
Stiffening up how , Freddy ?
First , I got a really fucked headache .
Then - - then my - - my stomach started cramping - - cramping up .
Now my arms and legs are cramping .
Let 's take a look . Let 's take a look .
[ cracking sound ]
Oh , God !
[ screams ]
Let 's get his shirt up , huh ?
What are you doing , Ernie ?
Oh , God .
Uh , the bruises where he 's lying down ,
uh ,
that 's blood pooling up .
[ cracking ]
Easy . Easy . Easy !
Okay .
You know , it looks like
rigor mortis is setting in .
Rigor mortis ? What do you mean , rigor mortis ?
Hey , God , you 're dead .
You 're dead , and you 're gonna turn into one of those things out there !
No !
- No ! - No !
- Let him go ! - Son of a bitch !
Shut - - Just shush !
[ sirens wail ]
Do you hear that ?
What is that ?
It 's another paramedic ambulance .
[ tires screech ]
Watch out ! Watch out !
Hey ! Don 't go over there !
Brains !
God damn !
Fuck . They 're gonna kill everybody that comes here .
[ crashing ]
[ corpses yell ]
Watch out , I 'm going to put the board back up .
[ screams ]
It 's got me !
Get this thing out of here !
Pull her off ! Pull her off !
Christ .
Damn , he 's dead . Shit . Shit .
What do we do with this thing ?
What do we do with this ?
Just - - just wait there a second .
Let 's get out of here .
Where the fuck is he going ?
Ernie , what are you doing ?
Hey !
[ gargling sound ]
Let me take it ! Let me take it !
You can let go of it now .
Are you crazy ?
Look at it . She looks better now .
Better .
We got to get out of here , Ernie .
Ernie , we got to get the fuck out of here .
Leave it .
What are you doing ? Goddamn it , Ernie !
I don 't understand what you want with it , Ernie .
- What are we doing with it ? - I want to examine it .
You make sure it 's tied right .
It 's being tied right .
I mean , it 's not gonna get loose , right ?
No , it 's not gonna get loose .
They 're no stronger than humans .
Don 't be afraid .
I 'll bust it in the damn head .
Now , you sure that thing 's tied good ?
- You can hear me ? - Yes .
Why do you eat people ?
Not people , brains .
Brains only ?
Yes .
Why ?
The pain .
What about the pain ?
The pain of being dead .
It hurts to be dead .
I can feel myself rot .
Eating brains
how does that make you feel ?
It makes the pain go away .
Hey , look , man , fuck this .
I got to talk to you . Now .
Come on , I got to talk . We got to talk .
No , let 's talk out in the hall .
[ groans ]
Look , how can we kill those things ?
You don 't .
What the fuck do you mean , " you don 't " ?
You can 't kill those mothers , they 're already dead .
You 've gotta understand they 're not living creatures , they 're animated .
You can chop them up into pieces , the pieces will still come after you .
All you can do is just burn them .
You got to totally reduce them to ashes ,
so there 's nothing left to come after you .
How you gonna burn all those things ?
Man , there 's 100 of those fuckers .
Yeah , that is the question .
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ We 'll make love till we die ♪
[ squeak ]
We have a 10-32 from EMS .
Two , repeat , two paramedic vehicles
missing in the East Piedmont district .
Request a 10-51 , code 3 .
Available units near the 20,000 block
of East Central , please respond , over .
Do you think they 'll rescue us ?
They better , man . That 's all I got to say .
[ distant shouting and moaning ]
Oh , God , please .
But do you think they will ?
[ sobs ]
Chuck ?
I never did like you .
Oh , my God , hold me tight .
Look , I think it 'd be a lot wiser
if we , say , contained Frank and Freddy .
You know what I 'm saying ?
No , what do you mean , " contained " ?
What I mean is lock them in a room , so if they started
acting funny , they wouldn 't hurt anybody .
They don 't want to hurt anybody .
You bastard ! Why don 't you lock yourselves up ?
Look , lady , we 're not proposing doing anything to them , for Christ 's sake .
We just want to lock them in another room so we can figure out
how to get the hell out of here . Alright ?
Tina , that really is a good idea .
Where can we put them , Ernie ?
Uh , yeah , well , uh , the chapel .
All right , help me with Frank , please .
- Lift his feet . - Come on .
[ screams ]
On the rug .
Lay them on the carpet , gently .
Easy .
Easy , Frank . It 's all right . Can you hear me , Frank ?
Oh , boy , he 's gone .
[ Tina sobs ]
Oh , Freddy .
Look , let 's just leave them and get out .
I 'm not leaving Freddy .
We got to lock the door , you know that ?
I 'm staying .
Okay . Come on .
Come on , Ernie .
Dispatch , dispatch . This is bravo 751 .
We 're at the mortuary .
We see two , that is two ,
paramedic vehicles parked in the rear parking lot .
The doors on one vehicle are hanging open .
Stand by while we investigate . Over .
[ muffled radio chatter ]
[ cocks gun ]
I got a man down .
Ah , Jesus !
Hold it right there !
Freeze or I 'll blow your fucking brains out !
[ screams ]
This place ...
Everybody that comes in gets swallowed up .
Send more cops .
Well , what are we gonna do ? Stand here , beating our meat till
the corpses bust in this damn place ?
There ain 't no way to stop those things . We gotta get the fuck out .
We got to get to the cars .
There 's corpses all over the cars .
- I know that . - What are you proposing ?
What am I proposing ? I think we all should do some damn proposing .
The crawlspace in the ceiling .
We could go up , barricade ourselves in .
The only way up is the hatch , and we could nail that shut .
You must be out of your fuckin ' mind .
I 'm not barricading myself in no damn roof .
Shit , I 'd rather take my chances with the cars .
We need a way to fight them .
How about this ?
What is that ?
It 's nitric acid . Pretty much destroy anything .
Yeah , but there 's not - - not enough of it , Ernie .
[ screams ]
It hurts !
It hurts more than you can imagine .
I know .
Freddy !
[ sobs ]
I can finally see
the one thing
the one thing that can relieve this horrible suffering .
What , Freddy ? What ?
Live brains !
[ screams ]
Let 's go .
Brains ! [ screams ]
[ screams ]
Get the girl !
Run !
Put her on the couch .
They got Freddy .
It was horrible , ugly , man .
His face was all fucked up .
His face - -
He 's not Freddy .
Brains . Brains . Brains .
Make her shut up . Make her shut up !
[ crash ]
Brains .
Brains . Brains . Brains .
Shit , he 's trying to get out .
Get a bench , come on .
Ernie !
Ernie , out of the way !
Bring it against it . It 's all right .
I can 't .
Yes , you can . Get up !
We can 't stay here , man . It 's gonna bust through that door .
We got to run for the cars .
There 's zombies all over the cars outside .
Got to fight our way through them , there 's no other way .
Once we 're in the car and moving , I think we 'll be all right .
That 's a big fucking " if , " man .
I can 't walk , much less run .
How bad is your foot , Ernie ?
Broke .
[ screams ]
Spider and I 'll get one of the cars , we 'll bring it up near the door .
Police car . It should still have the keys in the ignition .
Son of a bitch . The motor is still running .
Good . I 'll drive .
- No , I 'll drive . - Hey , fuck you .
When we drive up , I don 't want to hang out there longer than necessary .
Young lady , you stand right here . Put one hand here , one hand here .
When I say " now , " you open that door fast .
The minute we 're through , you slam that door hard and lock it .
Ernie ,
get your ass over here at the door .
Burt ...
That favor that you owe me . Watch your ass out there .
All right , you stand by .
Now !
Run ! Run !
Get ' em !
[ honks horn ]
You got to get closer , man . They 'll never make it like this .
We got to split . We got to split .
No , we can 't split .
[ screams ]
They left us , those jerks !
They left us !
They had to .
Burt will send help .
I know him .
They left us .
What are you doing ? We can 't just leave ' em !
They 'd have turned the goddamn car over .
We 'll send help .
Bullshit ! Those are my fucking friends .
I said we 'll send help , man .
- Coward ! - Fuck you !
Hang on , here we go !
What the fuck are we gonna do now ?
Find a phone , call the cops .
What the fuck ?
Jesus H. Christ !
Shit !
[ corpses scream ]
Back to the warehouse !
[ tires screech ]
Shit !
This way , you stupid honky !
That 's Spider .
[ corpses scream ]
Shit ! Hey , Spider !
Hey , hey ! Where is everybody ?
I don 't know .
- Who 's he ? - He owns this place .
That fucking car is totaled , man .
That 's all right . My car is still out there . So is Frank 's .
[ car explodes ]
Not anymore .
[ screams ]
[ pounding on door ]
[ corpse screams ]
[ grunts ]
Tina !
Tina , where are you ?
Forgive me .
[ screams ]
[ sirens wail ]
- Brains ! - Cops ! Get ' em !
[ screams ]
Ground , this is air 3 , we got a bad situation .
We 've got officers down .
We have just witnessed ground units attacked . Repeat , attacked .
Helicopter !
Attention . Attention . This is the police .
[ man over speaker ] This area is under police blockade .
All persons within this area
wishing to surrender should make their way
to the perimeter at once .
Jesus .
It sounds like the shit 's really hitting the fan out there .
Man , we got to let them know we 're in here .
You better believe it .
Hey , mister !
Don 't go in there .
There 's a thing in there , and it ripped out the phone .
There 's another phone in the basement .
The basement 's fucked ! You know what 's in the basement ?
- What do you mean ? - One of those corpses , man .
A real ugly one , all black and slimy .
I don 't give a shit what 's in the basement , we got to get to that phone .
Blinding them seems to work okay , doesn 't it ?
[ sirens wail ]
Wait a minute . Wait a minute .
Spider , open the door .
I 'm going to knock his goddamn block off .
Tina , it was wrong for you to lock me up .
I had to hurt myself to get out .
But I forgive you , darling .
And I know you 're here ,
because I can smell your brains .
[ sobs ]
Go away !
I 'm coming up , Tina .
[ screams ]
[ pounding on door ]
Freddy !
See ?
And now you made me hurt myself again .
You made me break my hand completely off this time , Tina .
But I don 't care , darling ,
because I love you .
And you 've got to let me eat your brain .
[ doorknob rattles ]
Open the goddamn door .
Brains !
[ screams ]
Get him down .
All right , you guys , go . Get in there , come on , fast . Get in !
Watch it , the step 's out .
Jesus Christ .
That 's our friend . The Tarman got him .
Yeah . Give me the police .
It 's an emergency , operator .
Captain , over here .
Two more cars around the side .
Yes , go ahead .
Yeah , you 've got to help us .
There 's a bunch of us trapped inside your barricade , and we can 't get out .
First of all , mister , what the hell is going on in there ?
I lost a dozen good men , and nobody can tell me jack shit .
There are people in the cemetery
who are stark , staring mad .
They 'll kill you and eat you .
It 's like a disease , like rabies , only faster . A lot faster .
That 's why you got to come in here now
and get us the hell out of here . Please !
Just a minute , I can 't hear you . There 's a lot of noise out here .
Hey , what the hell 's going on ?
Halt ! I said halt !
- Watch it . - They 're crazy !
[ gun fire ]
Oh , shit !
- No ! - Fuckers !
[ screams ]
[ voices screaming ]
- What ? - What is it ?
Cops . They 've got the cops .
That means they 're breaking out of the barricade .
Jesus Christ .
What 's he doing ?
What are you doing ?
Shh .
[ rings ]
Hello ?
Yeah , I 'm calling the number stenciled on the side of the tank .
Your name , please ?
Burt Wilson .
Stay on the line , Mr. Wilson . You 're being transferred .
This is Com-Q , Denver , go ahead .
Denver , this is Wichita . I 've got a C-L-Y priority on a 1-1-3 . Who 's up ?
That would be Col. Glover , San Diego . I 'll put you through .
[ buzzing ]
Yes ?
Yes , Captain .
- I see . Very well . - Horace .
- Put the call through to me . - What is it ?
Yes , yes , put him on .
Mr. Wilson , where are you calling from ?
I see . When did this take place ?
And when was the tank first breached ?
Why didn 't you call this number immediately ?
I see . It 's understandable . Wh-what happened next ?
Uh-huh .
Oh , you did ? And what effect did that have ?
I see .
So , uh , what did you do then ?
And what did they do ?
I see .
Really ? How many did you say ?
And how many acres does this cemetery cover , sir ?
Yes .
I see .
Yes , I see . Of course .
Uh , thank you for your assistance , Mr. Wilson .
I 'm going to switch you back to Captain Turner now . He 'll talk to you .
[ printing ]
Sir , this is Col. Glover .
I 'm sorry to disturb you at this hour , but we 're at Q-2 status .
It looks like we 've found that lost consignment of easter eggs .
[ printing ]
Yes , sir , pretty sure .
They 've turned up in Louisville .
I 'm getting confirmations on this from the Louisville Police Department .
Louisville , Kentucky , sir .
Well , sir , it would be good news ,
except that the eggs have hatched .
What are they doing , man ?
Hang on a second , would you ?
I dunno . It 's weird . These people seem to say
th-they 've been waiting for this to happen .
Apparently , they 've got some sort of
contingency plan to deal with it .
Well , that 's great !
What is this plan ?
Sgt. Jefferson , 42nd Special Mobile Artillery . Yes , sir .
Good morning to you , too , sir .
Yes , sir . All right , sir .
Whatever you say , sir . The code numbers please , sir .
Archimedes . Hotdog . Rhubarb .
Niner . Zero . Niner . Gotcha , sir .
Bearing . Mark 2-2-0 .
Bearing , 2-2-0 .
Range . Mark 134 miles .
Range , 1-3-4 miles .
[ warning siren ]
[ missile approaches ]
Hey , listen .
You hear anything ?
Tina-a-a-a .
[ explosion ]
Spectacular result , sir .
Very close to optimal placement .
Well , sir , only 20 square blocks destroyed .
Less than 4,000 dead , General .
I wouldn 't worry about the fires , General .
The rain is taking care of that right now .
Well , there have been complaints about burning skin ,
but I shouldn 't worry .
Minor irritation , General .
The rain will wash everything away .
That 's correct , sir . All should be back to normal by morning .
Yes , sir , I understand the President
will visit Louisville tomorrow .
No , no , we wouldn 't want that to happen , sir .
No , sir , this hasn 't been very pleasant for anyone .
Thank you , sir . Goodnight , sir .
[ moaning and screaming ]
[ pounding ]
♪ Do you wanna party ♪
♪ It 's party time ♪
More brains !
- What are we gonna do ? - We 're gonna kill it !
[ dog yelps ]
It 's all over everything .
Stupid asshole !
Watch your tongue , if you like this job .
Like this job ?
Burt ? Frank .
We have a little problem .
[ screams ]
Ahh !
Do you ever fantasize
about being killed ?
Yeah !
The brain ! The brain !
I hit the fucking brain .
How do you kill something that 's already dead ?
Well , how do I know , Fred ? I don 't know , let me think .
It 's not a bad question , Burt .
What do you think this is about ?
You think this is a fuckin ' costume ? This is a way of life !
Man , there 's 100 of those fuckers .
[ both ] 100 ?
Brains !
Send more cops .
Goddamn !
I-I-I think things are getting out of hand .
Oh !
Get it off ! Get it off !
It worked in the movie .
Well , it ain 't working now .
You mean the movie lied ?
It 's not a bad question , Burt .
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ We 'll make love till we die ♪
♪ Ooh , baby , your ♪ ♪ asphalt eater hung ten ♪
♪ The hoedads and gremmies ♪ ♪ say you reached top end ♪
♪ So do the dead , through the lights ♪
♪ The surf in ' dead , ooh , make it tight ♪
♪ The livin ' dead , now , ♪ ♪ baby , lose their heads ♪
♪ Now , baby , doin ' the dead ♪
♪ You square brain 's out ♪ ♪ there , better beware ♪
♪ Oh , this phantom driver ♪ ♪ down in the ground ♪
♪ You better plant ' em right ♪ ♪ or they 'll come around ♪
♪ Move out , baby , move that mound ♪
♪ Or they 'll dig it up ♪ ♪ and they 'll shut you down ♪
♪ So c 'mon , aw c 'mon , aw c 'mon ♪
♪ Aw c 'mon , aw c 'mon ♪
♪ Aw c 'mon , aw c 'mon ♪ ♪ aw c 'mon , aw c 'mon ♪
♪ Now , life is short and ♪ ♪ it 's filled with stuff ♪
♪ So let me know , baby , ♪ ♪ when you 've had enough ♪
♪ Oh , do the dead , turn blue ♪
♪ Yeah , the surf in ' ♪ ♪ dead , as dead as you ♪
♪ There 's nothing on the ♪ ♪ radio when you 're dead ♪
♪ There 's nothing at the movie show ♪
♪ When you 're dead ♪
♪ There 's nowhere left for you to go ♪
♪ Do the dead , yeah , do the dead ♪
♪ Do the dead ♪